Blood In. Blood Out.
Blood Out is a action, thriller film directed by Jason Hewitt.
When big city detectives refuse to further investigate his kid brother's gang related murder, small town Sheriff
Michael Spencer drops the badge and goes undercover to find his brother's killer and avenge his death.
Detective Hardwick, played by 50 Cent.
Arturo, played by Val Kilmer.
Michael, played by Luke Goss.
Zed, played by Vinnie Jones.
Anya, played by AnnaLynne McCord.
Elias, played by Tamer Hassan.
Blood Out is a 2011 American direct-to-video action
film written by Jason Hewitt and John A.
O'Connell and starring Val Kilmer and Luke Goss.
The film is Hewitt's directorial debut.
The tone is intense.